<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sumei Yao</title>
    <link>https://sumeiyao.github.io/docs/AboutMe/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sumei Yao</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://sumeiyao.github.io/docs/AboutMe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sumeiyao.github.io/docs/AboutMe/Education-and-Honors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sumeiyao.github.io/docs/AboutMe/Education-and-Honors/</guid>
      <description>Education # 2024.04-2025.04, Exchange Ph.d Student at ETH Zürich, Switherland 2021.09-2024.04, Ph.d Candidate of Wuhan University, China SELECTED GRANTS AND HONORS # China Scholarship Council jointly training doctoral program, July 2024 Outstanding Graduate of Hebei Province, Apr. 2021 National Scholarship for Graduate Student, Dec. 2020 National Scholarship for Graduate Student, Dec. 2019 National Encouragement Scholarship, Sept. 2016 National College Students e-commerce &amp;ldquo;Innovation, Creativity and Entrepreneurship&amp;rdquo; Challenge Final, National Third Prize, Sept.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sumeiyao.github.io/docs/AboutMe/Research-Interests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sumeiyao.github.io/docs/AboutMe/Research-Interests/</guid>
      <description>Research Interests # Key Areas # Extraction, mining, and organization of biomedical literature and user-centric document systems Building stable, robust disease prediction models Analyzing, monitoring, and identifying sentiments, behaviors, and topics of vulnerable populations/patients on social media Types of Data # Full text of Scientific Literatures in large scale Comprehensive electronic health records from hospitals and health organizations Disease-related posts and behavioral data from largeß-scale social media platforms Research Methodology # I lean towards quantitative approaches, integrating techniques such as :</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
